Your company has a problem
you don't even know about.
Your Employee Handbook says
passwords need twelve characters.
Your Security Policy says fourteen.
Which one is right?
Until today, you'd never know.
Introducing DocOps Agent.
This isn't a chatbot.
This is an intelligent agent that thinks.
Watch. I click one button, and DocOps
launches a multi-step analysis.
First, it searches your entire document corpus
using hybrid search,
combining keyword matching
with semantic understanding.
Then it compares related sections
across documents,
looking for conflicts that simple
pattern-matching would miss.
Five tools. One agent. Zero manual work.
Here's what it found.
Twenty-three issues across fifty documents.
In under two minutes.
Look at this conflict.
The Remote Work Policy says employees
can work from anywhere.
But the Data Security Policy requires
customer data work on approved networks only.
A remote employee handling customer data
would violate security policy,
but there's no obvious keyword conflict.
DocOps understood the implication.
That's semantic conflict detection.
No other tool does this.
Under the hood, this is pure Elasticsearch power.
Hybrid search combines BM25 keyword matching
with dense vector embeddings.
Every document is chunked, embedded,
and indexed for lightning-fast retrieval.
The agent uses six custom tools,
all powered by Elasticsearch queries.
Aggregations analyze conflict patterns.
Runtime fields calculate staleness dynamically.
This is what Elasticsearch Agent Builder
was made for.
Multi-step reasoning. Tool orchestration.
Real intelligence.
But finding problems is only half the battle.
DocOps generates compliance reports
automatically.
Conflicts grouped by severity.
Staleness analysis. Coverage gaps.
Every alert includes remediation suggestions.
Not just "here's a problem,"
but "here's how to fix it."
And everything is logged for audit trails.
Timestamp. Action. Result.
Ready for compliance review.
Twenty-three critical issues.
Fifty documents analyzed.
Two minutes.
A compliance team would spend weeks
doing this manually.
And they'd still miss
the semantic conflicts.
DocOps Agent.
Built with Elasticsearch Agent Builder.
Intelligent document operations
for the enterprise.
Find conflicts. Fix compliance. Sleep better.